<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jeet&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://jeetelongname.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jeet&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>copyright © Jeetaditya Chatterjee 2020-2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 22:01:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jeetelongname.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Roasted vegetables. A retrospective</title>
      <link>https://jeetelongname.github.io/blog/posts/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 22:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeetelongname.github.io/blog/posts/post2/</guid>
      <description>Roasting Vegetables is great! its a great way to get rid of those lingering vegetables and its simple and quick to do! I see it as a fridge cleaner and an easy way to make a simple side. (but i end up eating them on its own!)
Prerequisites There are no hard and fast rules when it comes to this. But i like to add in
  At least one onion like vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get started with Hugo and GitHub</title>
      <link>https://jeetelongname.github.io/blog/posts/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeetelongname.github.io/blog/posts/post1/</guid>
      <description>I am no expert I should start this by saying I started this website a good year ago and did nothing with it. I was adamant that I would do everything in wrought HTML ,lets just say that was a massive mistake. I ended up settling on a simple home page with a hugo blog to power the back-end. After multiple hiccups with finding a theme i had settled on Tokiwa for a while and all was well&amp;hellip; that was until i tried blogging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://jeetelongname.github.io/blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeetelongname.github.io/blog/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi I am Jeet! I am a Student that is studying computer science at 6th form This is my Blog!
Thats well and good but whats it about? I use Linux, and I cook, this is what I will write about when I find the time. I am constantly experimenting with new pieces of software and will probably write about them at some point.
How can I berate you about how you are wrong?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>