<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jeet&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jeet&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy 2022 Jeetaditya Chatterjee</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Moving to Wayland! Login shell lambasting</title>
      <link>https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/moving-to-wayland1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/moving-to-wayland1/</guid>
      <description>The problem I have been trying to move to Wayland for the past year. The call of gestures, less artifacting and just the hype had me spell bound. The problem was, GNOME, my DE of choice, decided to make what I think is the asinine choice to not start the DE in a login shell. All this meant was my .profile never runs and my nix environment never get set up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr Strange: Movie of madness</title>
      <link>https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/dr-strange-critique/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/dr-strange-critique/</guid>
      <description>I recently, like a lot of people, watched the new Dr Strange movie. I found it&amp;hellip; underwhelming to say the least. Even though it looked great I left that movie hall feeling like I just watched an underused mess. It was almost not as fun as having to deal with the ire of my family, as I was the one who chose the movie&amp;hellip;
BTW this is an adaptation from a long discord message I posted in the doom emacs discord server so&amp;hellip; Hi Lejon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2am paella</title>
      <link>https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/2am-paella/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/2am-paella/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its 2am and your hungry, but you look in the noodle cupboard and you realise
your out of instant ramen 😱.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I have not blogged as much as I have wanted too</title>
      <link>https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/why-i-have-not-written/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/why-i-have-not-written/</guid>
      <description>This blog has been a bit quiet. I enjoy writing about things, I have many things to write about, but I never do. Why is that? This is a kind of rambling dive into some of the reasons I have noticed.
My tools I dislike the blogging system I have chosen. Hugo is a fine piece of work don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, but for me it feels incomplete in a certain sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List manipulation into madness</title>
      <link>https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/post4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/post4/</guid>
      <description>It all started from a joke.. A friend sent me a code snippet in an effort to prank meme. To bad for him I know that url by heart and was not fooled by his petty gambit. But this got me thinking about ways of shrinking his solution and ended up with me finding different ways to manipulate the same list into doing the same thing. I hope you find this journey as interesting as I did!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roasted vegetables. A retrospective</title>
      <link>https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 22:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/post2/</guid>
      <description>Roasting Vegetables is great! its a great way to get rid of those lingering vegetables and its simple and quick to do! I see it as a fridge cleaner and an easy way to make a simple side. (but i end up eating them on its own!)
Prerequisites There are no hard and fast rules when it comes to this. But i like to add in
  At least one onion like vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get started with Hugo and GitHub</title>
      <link>https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/post1/</guid>
      <description>I am no expert I should start this by saying I started this website a good year ago and did nothing with it. I was adamant that I would do everything in wrought HTML ,lets just say that was a massive mistake. I ended up settling on a simple home page with a hugo blog to power the back-end. After multiple hiccups with finding a theme i had settled on Tokiwa for a while and all was well&amp;hellip; that was until i tried blogging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jeetelongname.net/blog/posts/blog/</guid>
      <description>Posts  2am paella&amp;#xa0;&amp;#xa0;&amp;#xa0;cooking&amp;#xa0;cheap&amp;#xa0;easy  Introduction  Its 2am and your hungry, but you look in the noodle cupboard and you realise your out of instant ramen 😱.
Here is a quick way to eat some vegetables, prep some soul filling food and have nummies done in 20ish minutes (which is not bad for something from scratch). This is not a traditional recipe, It kinda is similar but its not authentic in any way, shape or form.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
